<webscript>
   <shortname>POST account</shortname>
   <description><![CDATA[
   POSTing an email address to this webscript is an implicit request to create an account for that user e.g. joe.bloggs@eng.acme.com
   The user "joe.bloggs" will be added to the account associated with the domain "eng.acme.com". If such an account does not
   exist, it may be created (subject to validation of the domain).<br/>
   The Content-Body should have the form:
<pre>
    {
       "email":           "joe.bloggs@eng.acme.com",
       "firstName":       "Joe",
       "lastName":        "Bloggs",
       "password":        "mypassword",
       "source":          "website",
       "sourceUrl":       "http://www.alfresco.com/products/cloud",
       
       "ipAddress":       "100.100.100.100",
       "landingTime":     1321010076,
       "landingReferrer": "format TBD",
       "landingPage":     "format TBD",
       "landingKeywords": ["key1", "key2", "key3"],
       "utmSource":       "format TBD",
       "utmMedium":       "format TBD",
       "utmTerm":         "format TBD",
       "utmContent":      "format TBD",
       "utmCampaign":     "format TBD"
    }
</pre>
<ul>
<li>email: The email address of the user signing up. Mandatory.</li>
<li>firstName: The last name of the user signing up. Optional.</li>
<li>lastName: The first name of the user signing up. Optional.</li>
<li>password: The password of the user signing up. Optional.</li>
<li>source: The source of the signup e.g. mobile app, website etc. Mandatory.</li>
<li>sourceUrl: For the case where source is website, the URL of that website can be specified here. e.g. http://www.alfresco.com/products/cloud. Optional.</li>
<li>ipAddress: The IP address from which the user signed up. Optional.</li>
<li>landingTime: The UNIX time (in seconds) the user originally landed on the website. Optional.</li>
<li>landingReferrer: The landing referral URL where the user came from. Optional.</li>
<li>landingPage: The landing page the user first arrived on the website. Optional.</li>
<li>landingKeywords: The landing keywords if the user arrived from a search engine. Optional.</li>
<li>utmSource: Google 'source' identifier. Optional.</li>
<li>utmMedium: Google 'medium' identifier. Optional.</li>
<li>utmTerm: Google 'term' identifier. Optional.</li>
<li>utmContent: Google 'content' identifier. Optional.</li>
<li>utmCampaign: Google 'campaign' identifier. Optional.</li>
</ul>
The source along with any optional properties whose values are given will be used for signup metrics. The presence of firstName,
lastName and password implictly imply that the registration is "preRegistered". 
   ]]>
   </description>
   <url>/internal/cloud/accounts/signupqueue</url>
   <format default="json">argument</format>
   <authentication runas="admin">none</authentication>
   <transaction>required</transaction>
   <lifecycle>internal</lifecycle>
</webscript>